I've realised is, I don't think it's
fair to ask your nearest and dearest
to read the stuff that you've written.
I just don't. And part of the reason
is because of that tenth of an arse thing,
right? If you're asking people to
read stuff that you've written,
they're used
to reading Finnish stuff.
They don't have, they don't have any
kind of handle on reading stuff that's
not finished. And so I
think one of the things
that you can do, one of the
most helpful things you can do,
is to find somebody,
probably somebody who's somewhere on the
same journey as you trying to write,
that's prepared to read
what you've written.
And again, don't throw
an entire novel at them.
Like, you know, as I said, we're
doing like two hours a week.
That's tops.